From online stalking... to real life hell.
Lover, Stalker, Killer is a crime, documentary film directed by Sam Hobkinson.
In this twisting documentary, a mechanic tries online dating for the first time
and meets a woman who takes romantic obsession to a deadly extreme.
Self - Stalking Victim, played by Dave Kroupa.
Self (archive footage), played by Liz Golyar.
Self (archive footage), played by Cari Farver.
Self - Dave's Ex-Partner, played by Amy Flora.
Self - Cari's Mother, played by Nancy Raney.
Self - Pottawattamie County Sheriff's Office, played by Ryan Avis.
Billy is a fictional character from the Black Christmas film series, first appearing in Black Christmas (1974) as
a deranged murderer who taunts and kills a group of college students during the Christmas season.
Created by Timothy Bond and A.
Roy Moore, the character was partly inspired by the urban legend "The Babysitter and the Man
Upstairs", in addition to the crimes of George Webster and the serial killer William Heirens.
Several members of the cast and crew portrayed and voiced Billy in the original film, such as Nick
Mancuso, who performed the voices for the phone calls, while cameraman Albert J.
Dunk performed Billy's POV shots and director Clark portrays
both the villain's shadow and the phone voices.
Neither the character nor his portrayers were listed in the end credits.
In the years following the original film's release, fans and media outlets have often cited the character's name
as Billy, and director Clark has himself referred to the character by that name in interviews.
Unlike later slasher film antagonists, Billy's true identity and motivations were intentionally omitted
from the 1974 version of the film, which the filmmakers felt made him more frightening.
Critics and art historians have stated that by leaving Billy enigmatic, it allowed the audience to place
their own fears onto the character, forming their ideas about him and his motivations.
While largely overshadowed by more popular horror or slasher film villains, Billy has also been identified by some critics and film historians as
establishing many of the tropes that later became a staple of the slasher film genre, predating John Carpenter's Halloween (1978).
He has been described by some writers as one of the greatest horror villains of all
time and has been referenced in several other entertainment media.
The film explores themes of ex-lover, stalking, female
stalker, true crime, text messaging.
The tone is mind_bending.